Preliminary Guide to the Washington State University College of Engineering Research Division Correspondence, Minutes, Reports, and Speeches circa 1940s-1970
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- Fabrication and Testing of Beams Containing Proof Loaded Tension Lam. (Box 11, Folder 673)
- Application of Polymers for Rock Bonding and Reinforcement of Coal Mine Structures (Box 12, Folder 674)
- The Application of Polymers for Rock Bonding and Reinforcement of Coal Mine Structures (Box 12, Folder 675)
- Develop Methods for the Commercial Beneficiation of Washington Sands (Box 12, Folder 676)
- Colville Andalusite Beneficiation Research (Box 12, Folder 677)
- Exploratory Study of Kaolin Clays (Box 12, Folder 678)
- Beneficiation of Stevens County Barite (Box 12, Folder 679)
- Investigation of the Properties of Arabinogalactan in Mineral Beneficiation (Box 12, Folder 680)
- 1967-68 Authorized Budgets - July 1, 1967 *** (Box 12, Folder 681)
- 1967-68 Authorized Budgets - Effective 7/1/67 (Box 12, Folder 682)
- Authorized Budgets 1967/68 - Jun (Jan?***) 1, 1968 Revision (Box 12, Folder 683)
- 1967-68 Midyear Budget Revisions (Box 12, Folder 684)
- Biennium Budget Forecasts 1961-1963 Original Section Forecasts (Box 12, Folder 685)
- Biennium Budget Forecasts 1963-1965 (Box 12, Folder 686)
- Section Annual Budget Forecasts 1963-1964 (Box 12, Folder 687)
- Budget Forecasts 1964/65 (Box 12, Folder 688)
- Budget Forecasts 1969/70 (Box 12, Folder 689)
- 1966/67 Authorized Budget (Box 12, Folder 690)
- 1966/67 Mid-year Budget Revision (Box 12, Folder 691)
- Design and Construction of a Wood Footbridge Employing a New Structural System (Box 13, Folder 692)
- Research Oriented Abstract Service Industrial Utilization of Wheat (Box 13, Folder 693)
- Survival of Intestinal Bacteria in Pristine Waters (Box 13, Folder 694)
- Light-Weight Surgical Casts (Box 13, Folder 695)
- Design and Construction of an Improved Electronic Music Synthesizer (Box 13, Folder 696)
- Design and Construction of an Improved Electronic Music Synthesizer (Box 13, Folder 697)
- Biological Impact of Combined Metallic and Organic Pollution in Coeur d'Alene, etc (Box 13, Folder 698)
- Model Development and Systems Analysis of the Yakima River Basin (Box 13, Folder 699)
- Est. of Low-Flow Criteria for Conservation, Recreation and **Aes. Purp. (Box 13, Folder 700)
- Flood Hydrograph for Ungagged Streams (Box 13, Folder 701)
- Columbia River as a Resource (Box 13, Folder 702)
- Pilto Project in Flood Plain Management (Box 13, Folder 703)
- Bioassays to Determine Algal Growth Potential of Micronutrients (Box 13, Folder 704)
- Controlling the Location and Dispersion of Thermal Polluting Effluents (Box 13, Folder 705)
- Heat Dissipation of Cooling Ponds (Box 13, Folder 706)
- Water Resources Research Studies of the State of Washington (Box 13, Folder 707)
- Computerized Management of Flood Plain Development (Box 13, Folder 708)
- ** Combustor Des.* to Reduce Pollutant Emissions from Kraft Rec. Furnaces (Box 13, Folder 709)
- Computer Representation of Interconnected Power Systems (Box 13, Folder 710)
- Wear of Engineering Materials (Box 13, Folder 711)
- Backscattering from an Imperfect-16 Conducting Loop (Box 13, Folder 712)
- High Power Radar for Troposphere Study (Box 13, Folder 713)
- Foliar Isoprene Emissions (Box 13, Folder 714)
- WSU Research Fund Carbon Dating Subsidy (Box 13, Folder 715)
- Development of a Language and Equipment for Oral Communication with a Computer (Box 13, Folder 716)
- Backscattering from Two Identical Circular Loops (Box 13, Folder 717)
- State Technical Services Program (Box 13, Folder 718)
- Initiation of a Research Program in Stress Wave Propagation (Box 13, Folder 719)
- Radio Frequency Utilization Conservation and Assignment, Phase I (Box 13, Folder 720)
- Air Pollution Indicator Plant Study in King County, Washington (Box 13, Folder 721)
- A Guide to Radioisotopes Applications (Box 13, Folder 722)
- Radio Frequency Utilization Conservation and Assignment, Phase III (Box 13, Folder 723)
- Improved Dynamic Deflection Measurement (Box 13, Folder 724)
- Asphalt Aggregate Study (Box 13, Folder 725)
- Development of River Basis Graphical Models and Streamflow Methodology (Box 13, Folder 726)
- Data Analysis for the Study Southwest Washington Study (Box 13, Folder 727)
- Studies to Determine Metabolism of Arabinolactam by Swine (Box 13, Folder 728)
- Microbaroms as Indicators of Wind Waves and Sea State (Box 13, Folder 729)
- Winds and Ionization in the Mesosphere and Lower Ioniosphere - Phase II (Box 13, Folder 730)
- Dairy Manure Management Methods (Box 13, Folder 731)
- Research on Composition and Distribution of Forest Fire Smoke (Box 13, Folder 732)
- Atmospheric Photochemical Reaction of Terpenes (Box 13, Folder 733)
- Evaluation of a New Cryogenic Sampler for Field Use (Box 13, Folder 734)
- Effects of Fluoride on Phosphorus Metabolism of Plants (Box 13, Folder 735)
- Response of Plant Fruiting of HF Fumigation (Box 13, Folder 736)
- Airborne Collection of Air Quality and Meteorological Data (Box 13, Folder 737)
- Water Reclamation by Reverse Osmosis (Box 13, Folder 738)
- An Integrated Study on the Impact of Metallic Trace Element Pollution in Coeur d'Alene - Spokane River (Box 13, Folder 739)
- Hydraulic Model Study (Box 13, Folder 740)
- Factors Affecting the Vibrational Parameters of Structural Lumber (Box 13, Folder 741)
- Geophysical Well Loggin for ARS (Box 13, Folder 742)
- Design and Construction of Watershed Models (Box 13, Folder 743)
- Implementing Research Results for Productors and Consumers of Forests Products (Box 13, Folder 744)
- Stress Wave Attenuation as an Indicator of Wood Strength (Box 13, Folder 745)
- Ceramic Tile - Preliminary Market Survey (Box 13, Folder 746)
- Preliminary Study on Interaction of Clay Minerals with Starch (Box 13, Folder 747)
- Blood Flow Studies Employing Laser-Doppler Flow Measuring Techniques (Box 13, Folder 748)
- Deve. Studies on Fiber Glass Shower Stalls (Box 13, Folder 749)
- Study of Process Variable in the Recovery Furnace, Black Liquor Oxidizer and Direct Contact Evaporators (Box 13, Folder 750)
- Study of Vancouver Lake (Box 13, Folder 751)
- Pollution Control Guideline Manual (Box 13, Folder 752)
- An Air Quality Survey for Skagit County, Washington (Box 13, Folder 753)
- Study f Veneer Dryer Emission (Box 13, Folder 754)
- Evaluating the Static Bending Strengths of Laminated Beams (Box 13, Folder 755)
- Internal Dynamic Stress Measurements (Box 13, Folder 756)
- Surface Resistance of Rough Boundaries (Box 13, Folder 757)
- Radiation Heat Transfer in a Nonisothermal Hydrogen Plasma (Box 13, Folder 758)
- Surface Resistance of Plane Boundaries Roughened with Discrete Geometric Shapes (Box 13, Folder 759)
- Supplemental Data for Biennial Request 1973-75 (Box 14, Folder 760)
- Remodeling of Third Floor - Dana Hall (Box 14, Folder 761)
- Hydraulic Bldg. Completion (Box 14, Folder 762)
- Air Pollution Laboratory - Heating and Ventilation Program (Box 14, Folder 763)
- Building Prints (Box 14, Folder 764)
- Institute of Technology Operating Policies and Procedures (Box 14, Folder 765)
- Proposed Program for Fiscal Period 1973-74 Hydraulics Research Section, Civil Engineering Department/Branch (Box 14, Folder 766)
- Long Range Goals Study 1967-1977 (Box 14, Folder 767)
- **Program for Hydrogeological Evaluation Geothermal Res.* (Box 14, Folder 768)
- Feasibility Studies on Generation of Furfural Nut Flour (Box 14, Folder 769)
- Steelam Beam Development (Box 14, Folder 770)
- Steemlam Beam Design Formulae. Development and Verification for Lindal Cedar Homes, Inc., Seattle, Washington (Box 14, Folder 771)
- Part I - Developing Equations for a Composite Wood-Steel Beam for Lindal Cedar Homes, Inc., Seattle, Washington (Box 14, Folder 772)
- Testing of Steelam Beams for Lindal Cedar Homes, Inc., Seattle, Washington (Box 14, Folder 773)
- Forced Cooling of Gas Insulated Cable Systems - Preliminary (Box 14, Folder 774)
- SF6 Gas-Insulated Systems (Box 14, Folder 775)
- Forced Cooling of Gas Insulated Cable Systems - Investigation (Box 14, Folder 776)
- Research and Development Program Underwater/Underground 345-KV Gas-Insulated Transmission Systems (Box 14, Folder 777)
- Underground Cable Heat Transmission (Box 14, Folder 778)
- Corrosion Studies on URD Installation (Box 14, Folder 779)
- Preliminary Study on Modification of Crystalline Structure of **Clay Min.*? (Box 14, Folder 780)
- Preparation of Light Weight Ceramic Ceiling Tile Specimens for ITE - Imperial Corporation (Box 14, Folder 781)
- Demonstration of Grading Lumber by Vibrations (Box 14, Folder 782)
- Pressure Impregnation of Local Areas in Structural Lumber (Box 14, Folder 783)
- NDT Analysis of Lumber for Prediction of Tensile Strength (Box 14, Folder 784)
- Study of Wood Trusses (Box 14, Folder 785)
- Studies on Direct Bury Transformers (Box 14, Folder 786)
- The Application of Polymers for Rock Bonding and Reinforcement of Coal Mines Structures Third Quarterly Report (December 25, 1971 to March 24, 1972) (Box 14, Folder 787)
- Miscellaneous Brochures on Laboratory Supplies and Equipment (Box 15)
- Dimensionless Unit Hydrograph Studies (Box 16, Folder 788)
- Investigation of Damaged Control Valve (Box 16, Folder 789)
- Corrosion and Contamination Analysis on Copper Tubing (Box 16, Folder 790)
- Development of a Non-Destructive Test of the Adhesive Bond in Wood Scarf Joints (Box 16, Folder 791)
- Development of a Non-Destructive Test of the Adhesive Bond in Wood Scarf Joints (Box 16, Folder 792)
- Effect of Pollutants on MiniAdak Fluoride Reagent (7/29/69) (Box 16, Folder 793)
- Water Reclamation from Sewage by solvent Extraction (Box 16, Folder 794)
- Some Characteristics of Anaerobic Digestion - PHS Grant (Box 16, Folder 795)
- Some Characteristics of Anaerobic Digestion (Box 16, Folder 796)
- Miscellaneous Supplies and Equipment for the Air Pollution Section (Box 16, Folder 797)
- Septic Tank Performance at Low Temperature (Box 16, Folder 798)
- USPHS Analysis (U.S.PHS - Jean Schumeman) (Box 16, Folder 799)
- Development of a Relief Map of the Columbia River Basin Project (Box 16, Folder 800)
- Development of a Relief Map of the Columbia River Basin Project (Box 16, Folder 801)
- Sphaerotilus Control in Waste Water (Utah-Idaho Sugar Company) (Box 16, Folder 802)
- New Products from Dried Peas (Box 16, Folder 803)
- Study of Quartz Infra Red Heaters in Preheat Laminating of Lumber (Box 16, Folder 804)
- Study of Quartz Infra Red Heaters in Preheat Laminating of Lumber (Box 16, Folder 805)
- Spectral Transmittance on Plastic (Box 16, Folder 806)
- Spectrographic Analysis (Box 16, Folder 807)
- Moisture and Oxygen Permeability of Plastic Film (Box 16, Folder 808)
- Fluoride Analysis (Irrigation-Experiment Station, Prosser) (Box 16, Folder 809)
- Harvey Air Pollution Studies - 1957 (Box 16, Folder 810)
- Chemical Analysis of Feed Samples (Box 16, Folder 811)
- Analysis of National Carbon Electrode Core (Box 16, Folder 812)
- Analysis of Compressed Air (Box 16, Folder 813)
- Analysis of Special Oil Samples (Box 16, Folder 814)
- Analysis of Ash from Turkey Eggs (Box 16, Folder 815)
- Vanadium Analysis On Phosphate Rock (Box 16, Folder 816)
- Analysis of String Finger and WSU Water (Box 16, Folder 817)
- Spectrochemical Analysis of Feeds and Feeds Supplements (Box 16, Folder 818)
- Police Investigation (Box 16, Folder 819)
- Water Analysis (Box 16, Folder 820)
- Analysis of Ash from Turkey Eggs (Box 16, Folder 821)
- Leaf and Soil Analysis (Box 16, Folder 822)
- Identification of Granular Substance (Box 16, Folder 823)
- Spectrographic Analysis of Archeological Samples (Department of Agriculture) (Box 16, Folder 824)
- Water Analysis (Department of Zoology) (Box 16, Folder 825)
- Water Analysis (Animal Science) (Box 16, Folder 826)
- Feed and Water Analysis (Animal Science) (Box 16, Folder 827)
- Spectrochemical Analysis of Pant Ash (Box 16, Folder 828)
- Paint Analysis: Hit-Run (Box 16, Folder 829)
- Water Analysis (Box 16, Folder 830)
- Cobalt 60 Irradiation Facility (Agronomy Department) (Box 16, Folder 831)
- Spectrographic Analysis (Box 16, Folder 832)
- Paint Analysis (Building and Grounds) (Box 16, Folder 833)
- Police Investigation: Malicious Mischief (Box 16, Folder 834)
- Adrenalin Analysis on Blood (Box 16, Folder 835)
- Spectrochemical Analysis of Soil and Water Sample (Box 16, Folder 836)
- Investigation of Distilled Water Tank Corrosion Problem (Box 16, Folder 837)
- Spectrochemical and Chemical Analysis of Nickel Compound (Box 16, Folder 838)
- Manganese Analysis on Feed Samples (Box 16, Folder 839)
- Monochromater Shield Tank (Reactor) (Box 16, Folder 840)
- U.S. Patent No. 2,944,542 Dana and Barnett (Research Corporation) (Box 16, Folder 841)
- Pyrolityc Degradation of Complex Fluoride in Plant and Animal Tissue (Box 16, Folder 842)
- An Investigation of Stabilization Pond Loadings in the Purification of Sewages (Project 260) (Box 16, Folder 843)
- An Investigation of Stabilization Pond Loadings in the Purification of Sewages (Project 260) (Box 16, Folder 844)
- Chemical and Spectrographic Analysis of Limestone (Box 16, Folder 845)
- Limestone Analysis (Box 16, Folder 846)
- Chemical and Spectrographic Analysis of Limestone (Box 16, Folder 847)
- Limestone Analysis (Box 16, Folder 848)
- Arson Investigation (Ephrata) (Box 16, Folder 849)
- Arson Investigation (Box 16, Folder 850)
- Arson Investigation (Box 16, Folder 851)
- Arson Investigation (Box 16, Folder 852)
- Police Investigation of Fire Problem (Box 16, Folder 853)
- Arson Investigation (Ray McDirmid, Deputy State Fire Marshall) (Box 16, Folder 854)
- Timber Trespass Investigation (Box 16, Folder 855)
- ** Study of U.H.F Speed Meters (VHF*?) (Box 16, Folder 856)
- Negligent Homicide (Box 16, Folder 857)
- Hit-Run Paint Comparison (Box 16, Folder 858)
- Drug Analysis (Box 16, Folder 859)
- Direct Shear Tests (Box 16, Folder 860)
- Impact Machine Calibration (Box 16, Folder 861)
- Washington Testing Laboratories (Box 16, Folder 862)
- Spectrochemical Analysis of Flue Dust (Box 16, Folder 863)
- Spectrochemical Analysis of Selected Samples (Box 16, Folder 864)
- Consolidation and Direct Shear Test (Box 16, Folder 865)
- Washington Testing Laboratories (Box 16, Folder 866)
- Displacement Calculations (Box 16, Folder 867)
- Displacement Calculations (Box 16, Folder 868)
- Arson Investigation (RP 586) (Box 16, Folder 869)
- Arson Investigation (Box 16, Folder 870)
- Arson Investigation (Box 16, Folder 871)
- Strength Properties of Douglas-Fir Wood (Box 16, Folder 872)
- Strength Properties of Douglas-Fir Wood (Box 16, Folder 873)
- Effective Control of Sunlight as Related to House Openings (Box 16, Folder 874)
- Effective Control of Sunlight as Related to House Openings (Box 16, Folder 875)
- Investigation of Dynamic Action on Kootenay Lake (Box 16, Folder 876)
- Investigation of Dynamic Action on Kootenay Lake (Box 16, Folder 877)
- Damper Fatigue Test - Willamette Vibration Dampers (Box 16, Folder 878)
- Fatigue Tests on Willamette Vibration Dampers (Box 16, Folder 879)
- Tie Rod Fracture Analysis (Box 16, Folder 880)
- Seismic Studies for Town of Albion (Box 16, Folder 881)
- Investigate Corrosion Problem (Box 16, Folder 882)
- Semiquantitative Spectrochemical Analysis of Ore Samples (Box 16, Folder 883)
- Exploratory Study of Beneficiation of Washington Ore (Box 16, Folder 884)
- Analyze Water Samples for Presence of Gasoline (Box 16, Folder 885)
- Aswan Dam Carbon-14 Dating (Box 16, Folder 886)
- Spray Compatibility (Box 16, Folder 887)
- **Study Problem - Setting of Concrete Continuing CuCisub 2 (Box 16, Folder 888)
- Bay Chemical Company (Box 16, Folder 889)
- Investigation of Zinc Sulfate Scum Problem (Box 16, Folder 890)
- Effect of Calcium Chloride on Concrete Setting Time (Box 16, Folder 891)
- Arson Investigation Almota (Box 16, Folder 892)
- Hydraulic Model Studies Jaybird Tunnel Upper American River (Box 16, Folder 893)
- Jaybird Tunnel and Penstosck - Investigate Site (Box 16, Folder 894)
- Vulcanized Fiber Overlay for Lumber (Box 16, Folder 895)
- Sulton Spillway Outlet Model (Box 16, Folder 896)
- Carbon Dating of Samples from Port Vila, New Hebrides (Box 16, Folder 897)
- Carbon Dating of Samples from Port Vila, New Hebrides (Box 16, Folder 898)
- Photo Micrography (Box 16, Folder 899)
- Photo Micrography of Wood Fibers (Box 16, Folder 900)
- Brick Investigation (Box 16, Folder 901)
- Feasibility Study of Non-Resonant Vibration Dumping (Box 16, Folder 902)
- Metallurgic Analysis of 0.22 caliber cartridge cases (Box 16, Folder 903)
- Rocky Reach Dam Model (Box 16, Folder 904)
- Student Honor Societies (Box 17, Folder 905)
- WSU Miscellaneous (Box 17, Folder 906)
- WSU Policy and Procedures (Box 17, Folder 907)
- WSU Placement Bureau (Box 17, Folder 908)
- WSU Administration Office and Statistics (Box 17, Folder 909)
- WSC College Catalog and Catalog Committee (Box 17, Folder 910)
- WSU Colleges - Schools Dept. - Miscellaneous (Box 17, Folder 911)
- Institute of Agricultural Sciences (Box 17, Folder 912)
- The Graduate School (Box 17, Folder 913)
- WSC Fellowship, Scholarships and Assistants (Box 17, Folder 914)
- WSC - ROTC - Army (Box 17, Folder 915)
- WSC - ROTC - Air Force (Box 17, Folder 916)
- WSC - ROTC - Miscellaneous (Box 17, Folder 917)
- Pakistan Project (Box 17, Folder 918)
- Research Corporation (Box 17, Folder 919)
- WSC Resident Instructional Staff (Box 17, Folder 920)
- Fraternity Welfare Advisory Committee (Box 17, Folder 921)
- Academic Committee (Box 17, Folder 922)
- WSC Budget and Budget Committee (Box 17, Folder 923)
- Educational Policies Committee (Box 17, Folder 924)
- Nuclear Reactor Committee (Box 17, Folder 925)
- WSU Patent Committee (Box 17, Folder 926)
- WSU Committee on Research (Box 17, Folder 927)
- WSU Space Priorities Committee (Box 17, Folder 928)
- WSU Ten year Plan Committee (Box 17, Folder 929)
- WSU Traffic Control Board (Box 17, Folder 930)
- Deans and Directors Meeting (Box 17, Folder 931)
- WSC I.T. Miscellaneous (Box 17, Folder 932)
- I.T. Faculty and Staff - Miscellaneous (Box 17, Folder 933)
- I.T. Faculty and Staff Prospects (Box 17, Folder 934)
- Annual Review and Tenure (Box 17, Folder 935)
- I.T. Physical Plant (Box 17, Folder 936)
- I.T. Budget - Reg. and Vouchers and ID's (1130) (Box 17, Folder 937)
- I.T. Travel File - TA - Vouchers (1130) (Box 17, Folder 938)
- WSU I.T. Inventory (Box 17, Folder 939)
- I.T. Surplus Property (Box 17, Folder 940)
- I.T. Consulting and Planning Committees (Box 17, Folder 941)
- I.T. Advisory Board Membership (Box 17, Folder 942)
- I.T. Advisory Board - Miscellaneous (Box 17, Folder 943)
- DIR Staff Meetings (Box 17, Folder 944)
- DIR Administrative Policies (Box 17, Folder 945)
- Commercial Laboratories (Box 17, Folder 946)
- DIR Finance and Budget (Box 17, Folder 947)
- DIR Project Ideas (Box 17, Folder 948)
- DIR Digital Computer (Box 17, Folder 949)
- DIR Network Analyzer (Box 17, Folder 950)
- DIR Aircraft Warning Light (Box 17, Folder 951)
- DIR Research Sections, Miscellaneous (Box 17, Folder 952)
- DIR - Air Pollution Section (Box 17, Folder 953)
- General (Box 18, Folder 954)
- 381A7 though A14.03 (Box 18, Folder 955)
- 381A14.4 through 22.2 (Box 18, Folder 956)
- 381A22.3 through A33 (Box 18, Folder 957)
- 381B1 through 10.02 (Box 18, Folder 958)
- 381B10.3 through B12 (Box 18, Folder 959)
- 381B13 through 14.7 (Box 18, Folder 960)
- 381B15 through B20 (Box 18, Folder 961)
- With Reference to Dow Chemical Plant for Kalama, Washington Area (Box 18, Folder 962)
- Utilization of Peas and Lentils (Box 18, Folder 963)
- The Cowlitz County Air Pollution Bulletin on Stations Circular 352, Reynolds Metals, Longview (Box 18, Folder 964)
- On Industrial Utilization of Wheat (Box 18, Folder 965)
- On Liaison with the Reynolds Aluminum Company (Box 18, Folder 966)
- The Harvey Fluorine Survey at the Dalles, September 1959. Circular Write-up (Box 18, Folder 967)
- Radiation survey with Recommendation for Safety and Opera- tional Improvement of X-Ray Radiation and Radiographic Room 37 (Box 18, Folder 968)
- The Disposition of Washington Manufactures Toward Establishing a Non-profit Research Institute (Box 18, Folder 969)
- T B23 (Box 18, Folder 970)
- Section Budget Forecast 1959/60 Start of Year (Box 19, Folder 971)
- Section Budget Forecast 1958/59 Mid-year, January 1, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 972)
- Section Budget Forecast 1958/59 October 1, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 973)
- Budget Allocation - Mid-year 1958-1959 (Box 19, Folder 974)
- Budget Allocation - Start of Year 1958-1959 (Box 19, Folder 975)
- Budget Allocation 1959/1960, July 1, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 976)
- Budget Allocation 1959/1960, July 1, 1959 (Desk Copy) (Box 19, Folder 977)
- Budget Allocation 1959/1960 Mid-year Revision (Box 19, Folder 978)
- Budget Allocation 1960/1961, July 1, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 979)
- Budget Allocation 1960/1961, January 1, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 980)
- Budget Allocation 1960/1961, January 3, 1961 (Desk copy) (Box 19, Folder 981)
- Investigation of Hydraulic Dispenser (Box 19, Folder 982)
- Spectrochemical Analysis of Mild Steel (Box 19, Folder 983)
- ** Analysis of Walnut Meats (Box 19, Folder 984)
- ** Analysis of Walnet Meats (Box 19, Folder 985)
- Oil Analysis (Box 19, Folder 986)
- Triaxial Testing of Sand Backfill Material (Box 19, Folder 987)
- Production of Flakes for Laboratory Use (Box 19, Folder 988)
- Schering Bridge Test on Potential Transformer (Box 19, Folder 989)
- Schering Bridge Test on Potential Transformer (Box 19, Folder 990)
- Segregation in Ferrochrome Casting (Box 19, Folder 991)
- Fluorine Analyses of Leaf Samples (Box 19, Folder 992)
- Spectrographic Analysis (Box 19, Folder 993)
- Analysis of Liquor for Presence of Narcotics (Box 19, Folder 994)
- Corrosion of Fuel Oil Tanks (Box 19, Folder 995)
- Corrosion Study on Steel Tank Selection (Box 19, Folder 996)
- Lecture and 3000 copies of Report on W.0.257 *? (Box 19, Folder 997)
- Corrosion of Fuel Oil Tanks (Box 19, Folder 998)
- Corrosion of Fuel Oil Tanks (Box 19, Folder 999)
- ** Flapveg *? Sample (Box 19, Folder 1000)
- Arson Investigation (Box 19, Folder 1001)
- Police Investigation - Arson (Box 19, Folder 1002)
- 3812 Minutes (Box 19, Folder 1003)
- 3812 2 (Box 19, Folder 1004)
- 381I 3 (Box 19, Folder 1005)
- 3812 6 (Box 19, Folder 1006)
- 381 W Dead (Box 19, Folder 1007)
- 381 A Dead (Box 19, Folder 1008)
- 381 A Dead (Box 19, Folder 1009)
- 381 A Dead (Box 19, Folder 1010)
- 381 A Dead (Box 19, Folder 1011)
- David Comen 381IA22.3 (Box 19, Folder 1012)
- 381 B Dead (Box 19, Folder 1013)
- 381 B Dead (Box 19, Folder 1014)
- 381 B Dead (Box 19, Folder 1015)
- 381 B Dead (Box 19, Folder 1016)
- 381 B Dead (Box 19, Folder 1017)
- 381 B Dead (Box 19, Folder 1018)
- 381 C Dead File (Box 19, Folder 1019)
- 381 D Dead (Box 19, Folder 1020)
- Budget Forecasts by Section 69/70, July 1, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 1021)
- 1969/70 Mid-year Budget Revisions (Box 21, Folder 1022)
- Section Budgets: 1969-1970 (7/1/69) (Box 21, Folder 1023)
- 1969-1970 Section Budgets Revisions of Jan. 1, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 1024)
- General Fiscal Statistics - 1969/1970 CII (Box 21, Folder 1025)
- Fiscal Information 7/1/67 - 6/31/68 (Box 21, Folder 1026)
- Faculty Evaluation (Box 21, Folder 1027)
- Minutes - Faculty Evaluation Committee (Box 21, Folder 1028)
- Draft (Box 21, Folder 1029)
- Classification and Compensation Plan for Non-Faculty Personnel (Box 21, Folder 1030)
- Mechanical Engineering - General (Box 21, Folder 1031)
- Mechanical Engineering - Completed TA's and RA's (Box 21, Folder 1032)
- Metallurgy - Completed TA's and RA's (Box 21, Folder 1033)
- Electrical Engineering - Completed TA's and RA's (Box 21, Folder 1034)
- Metallurgical Engineering - General (Box 21, Folder 1035)
- 1968/69 Mid-year Budget Revisions (Box 21, Folder 1036)